<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>University of Toronto Speech Group</title><link>https://utspeech.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on University of Toronto Speech Group</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-ca</language><atom:link href="https://utspeech.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Archive</title><link>https://utspeech.github.io/page/archive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://utspeech.github.io/page/archive/</guid><description>Date Speaker Affiliation Title/Link April 7, 2022 Emily Blamire Linguistics Linguistic and social factors of Voice Recognition March 3, 2022 Wenfu Bao Speech Pathology Standardized measures of auditory attention in monolingual and bilingual children February 17, 2022 Rachid Riad Département d'études cognitives, École Normale Supérieure, Paris Using machine learning to obtain spoken language biomarkers in Huntington's Disease November 18, 2021 Thomas St. Pierre Psychology Children's language attitudes and media October 7, 2021 Juliette Millet Université de Paris Predicting non-native speech perception using the Perceptual Assimilation Model and state-of-the-art acoustic models June 3, 2021 Insiya Bhalloo Rehabilitation Sciences May 6, 2021 Chandan Narayan LLL (York) Burst amplitude is affected by speaking rate: Cross-linguistic observations and implications.</description></item><item><title>Join Us</title><link>https://utspeech.github.io/page/join/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://utspeech.github.io/page/join/</guid><description>Online On top of posts to this site, meeting information will be distributed through our mailing list. We will also distribute Zoom links and passcodes through the mailing list for online attendance of meetings.
To join the mailing list, send an email to &amp;#32;&amp;#32; . The request to join will be reviewed by one of the members of the team.
In-person Those interested in attending meetings in-person may simply show up at Room 213 in Odette Hall.</description></item></channel></rss>